Louis Fabian Bachrach Papers
Louis Fabian Bachrach Papers
1950-1963
Bachrach, Louis Fabian, 1881-1963.
4.5 linear ft.
Papers of the American portrait photographer. Correspondence, holograph and typescript articles, interviews, speeches, and notes; published materials, including articles by and about Bachrach, clippings, pamphlets, and press releases; and photographs taken by Bachrach, his son Louis Fabian Bachrach, Jr., and his father David Bachrach. Correspondence includes that of Sherman Adams, Joseph Alsop, Stewart Alsop, Joseph S. Clark, John F. Collins, Walter Cronkite, Ralph E. Flanders, J. William Fulbright, Barry M. Goldwater, Conrad Hilton, Luther Hodges, Herbert Hoover, Walter Lippmann, Maurine Brown Neuberger, Jacqueline Onassis, Norman Vincent Peale, James Reston, George W. Romney, and Leverett Saltonstall.
148822
Biographical History
The Bachrach family has been in the commercial photography business for more than 140 years, and Bachrach Studios is believed to be the world's oldest continuously operating photography studio. The studio was instrumental in establishing the idea of formal portraiture, having made portraits of every American President since Abraham Lincoln.
David Bachrach (1845-1921) founded Bachrach Studios in 1868. His son Louis Fabian Bachrach (1881-1963) began his photographic career by working with his father in Washington and Baltimore and by helping several photographers in New York. Louis Fabian Bachrach, Jr. (1917-2010), known as Fabian Bachrach, introduced color photography to the studio in the 1950s, while his brother Bradford (1910 or 1911-1992) headed the company until 1978. Fabian's son Robert now (2017) heads the family business, while son Louis Fabian Bachrach III has his own independent portrait studio.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Louis Fabian Bachrach Papers consist of correspondence, subject files, writings, photographs, and a small amount of material added later.
Incoming correspondence contains letters received by Louis Fabian Bachrach, Sr. It is arranged alphabetically by the last name of the sender or organization. Outgoing correspondence contains carbon tyrescripts of letters sent by Bachrach.
Subject files contain material such as bills, cards, certificates, newspaper clippings, and notes.
Writings in the collection are in the form of manuscripts and published material. Manuscripts contains both handwritten and typescript manuscripts of interviews, speeches, notes, etc. by Louis Bachrach Sr. and others, including an essay by his grandaughter, entitled "The Most Interesting Person I Know." Published material contains magazine articles, newspaper clippings, books, pamphlets and press releases by and about Louis Bachrach.
Photographs contains portrait and other photographs taken by Louis Bachrach, his father David Bachrach, and his sons Bradford and Fabian (Louis Fabian Bachrach, Jr.).
Arrangement of the Collection
Incoming correspondence is arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Outgoing carbons are arranged chronologically. Subject files are arranged alphabetically. Manuscripts and published material are subdivided by type and author. Miscellaneous photographs are subdivided by photographer; photographs of notable individuals are filed together in no particular order.
Subject and Genre Headings
Photography; Adams, Sherman, 1899-1986.; Alsop, Joseph, 1910-1989.; Alsop, Stewart.; Bachrach, David.; Bachrach, Louis Fabian, 1881-1963.; Bachrach, Fabian, 1917-2010.; Clark, Joseph S.; Collins, John F., 1888-; Cronkite, Walter.; Flanders, Ralph E. (Ralph Edward), 1880-1970.; Fulbright, J. William (James William), 1905-1995.; Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-1998.; Hilton, Conrad N. (Conrad Nicholson), 1887-1979.; Hodges, Luther Hartwell, 1898-1974.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Lippmann, Walter, 1889-1974.; Neuberger, Maurine Brown, 1907-; Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1929-1994.; Peale, Norman Vincent, 1898-1993.; Reston, James, 1909-; Romney, George W., 1907-1995.; Saltonstall, Leverett, 1892-1979.; Photographers -- United States.; Photography, Artistic.; Photographs.; Portrait photography.; Presidents -- United States -- Portraits.; United States -- Officials and employees -- Portraits.; Articles.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Interviews.; Photographs.; Pamphlets.; Press releases.; Speeches (documents); Photographers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Bradford Bachrach, 1964-1971.
Inventory
- Incoming correspondence
  This series consists of correspondence received by Louis Fabian Bachrach, Sr. It is arranged alphabetically by the last name of the sender or organization.
  - Biographical material (Box 1)
  - A (Box 1)
  - Adams, Sherman (Box 1)
  - Alsop, Joseph (Box 1)
  - Alsop, Stewart (Box 1)
  - B-C (Box 1)
  - Clark, Joseph S. (Box 1)
  - Collins, John F. (Box 1)
  - Cronkite, Walter (Box 1)
  - Curtis, Laurence (Box 1)
  - D (Box 1)
  - Dane, John (Box 1)
  - E-F (Box 1)
  - Flanders, Ralph E. (Box 1)
  - Fulbright, J.W. (Box 1)
  - G (Box 1)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Box 1)
  - H (Box 1)
  - Harris & Ewing (Box 1)
  - Hilton, Conrad (Box 1)
  - Hodges, Luther H. (Box 1)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Box 1)
  - I-K (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 1)
  - Keyser, F. Ray (Box 1)
  - L (Box 1)
  - Lippmann, Walter (Box 1)
  - M-N (Box 1)
  - Neuberger, Maurine (Box 1)
  - Newcomen Society (Box 1)
  - O-P (Box 1)
  - Peabody, Endicott (Box 1)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent (Box 1)
  - R (Box 1)
  - Reston, James (Box 1)
  - Romney, George (Box 1)
  - S (Box 1)
  - Saltonstall, Leverett (Box 1)
  - Smith, Benjamin A. (Box 1)
  - T-W (Box 1)
  - Wilkins, Raymond S. (Box 1)
  - Condolences upon death of Louis Fabian Bachrach, Sr. (Box 1)
- Outgoing correspondence
  This series consists of carbon tyrescripts of letters sent by Louis Fabian Bachrach.They are arranged in chronological order.
  - [General], Dec. 14, 1950-June 12, 1963; 8 folders (Box 2)
  - "Letters to the Editor" (Box 2)
  - Undated (Box 2)
- Subject file
  This series consists of material such as bills, cards, certificates, newspaper clippings, notes, photographs, and programs. This material is arranged in alphabetical order according to physical type.
  - Baltimore, early photographs (Box 2)
  - Baltimore Polytechnic Institute, Class of '97 Reunions (Box 2)
  - Birthday cards (Box 2)
  - Brady, Matthew B. (Box 2)
  - Business transactions (Box 2)
  - Calling cards (Box 2)
  - Grand Mason certificate (Box 2)
  - Handwriting analysis material (Box 2)
  - "Junk Mail" (Box 2)
  - Lincoln at Hanover Junction (Pa.) (Va.) Controversy (Box 2)
  - Lincoln's Gettysburg Address re-enactment (Box 2)
  - Lincoln material, Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Massachusetts Consistory medal (Box 2)
  - Membership cards and certificates (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - "Mona Lisa" in U.S.A. (Box 3)
  - Notes (Box 3)
  - Obituaries for Louis Bachrach (Box 3)
  - Professional convention & dinner programs (Box 3)
  - Unitarian material (Box 3)
- Manuscripts
  This series consists of holograph and typescript manuscripts. Those written by Louis Bachrach are in alphabetical order by title or subject. Interviews and speeches by Bachrach are also arranged alphabetically by title or subject. Also included in this series are notes and a manuscript by his grandaughter.
  - By Louis Bachrach
    - Descriptions of various famous photographs (Box 3)
    - Gardening, Clematis (Box 3)
    - "Wild Flowers I Have Grown" (Box 3)
  - Interviews
    - Louis Bachrach on photography (Box 3)
  - Speeches by Louis Bachrach
    - Autobiographical (Box 3)
    - Bachrach, Inc. (Box 3)
    - Business in General (Box 3)
    - "Craftsmanship" (Box 3)
    - Europe (Box 3)
    - Introduction to Garden Club Speech (Box 3)
    - "Learning to Make Photographic Portraits" (Box 3)
    - Photography (Box 3)
    - Photographers' Convention in Chicago (Box 3)
    - "What I Think of Hats ?" (Box 3)
    - Work (Box 3)
  - Notes for speeches (Box 3)
  - Manuscripts by others
    - "The Most Interesting Person I Know" by Faith Kimball (grand-daughter) (Box 3)
- Published materials
  This series consists of magazine articles about Louis Bachrach which are arranged alphabetically. Articles by Bachrach and books are also in alphabetical order. Also in this series are newspaper clippings by Bachrach and newspaper clippings about Bachrach which are in alphabetical order. Pamphlets and press releases are also in this series.
  - Articles about Louis Bachrach
    - "Bachrach- A Corporate Image" (Box 3)
    - "Every President Since Lincoln Sat for the Bachrachs" (Box 3)
    - "The Flattering Camera" (Box 3)
    - "The Man Who Shoots Presidents" (Box 3)
    - Dean's Review "Personal Memo" (Box 3)
    - "Photo by Bachrach" (Box 3)
    - "Portraiture of Men" (Box 3)
    - "...Speaking of Pictures..." (Box 3)
  - Articles by Louis Bachrach
    - "Comments on Growing Clematis" (Box 3)
    - "How to Look Your Picture-Best" (Box 3)
    - "Portraiture as a Business" (Box 3)
    - "Should a Photographer be an Engraver ?" (Box 3)
    - "Studio Lighting for Portraits of Women" (Box 3)
    - "What's Wrong With Portraits ?- The Answer" (Box 3)
  - Article about Bradford Bachrach (Box 3)
  - Article by Bradford Bachrach
    - "The Bachrach Story" (Box 3)
  - Articles by others (Box 3)
  - Books
    - A History of Bachrach (Box 3)
    - Profiles & Portraits of American Presidents (Box 3)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - About Louis Bachrach and his Gardening (Box 4)
    - About Louis Bachrach at Pinehurst (Box 4)
  - Newspaper clippings by Louis Bachrach
    - "Clematis: Fact & Theory" (Box 4)
    - "Five Gardens" (Box 4)
    - "Informed Gardners Avoid Common Pitfalls" (Box 4)
    - "Off Again, On Again" (Box 4)
    - "Success Story of a Rugged Individualist" (Box 4)
    - "Wild Fowers Offer Many Possibilities" (Box 4)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
  - Pamphlets
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
  - Press releases about Louis Bachrach (Box 4)
- Photographs
  - Photographs by David Bachrach
    - Annapolis (Box 4)
    - "Annapolis- Officers at Chapel" (Box 4)
    - Baltimore (Box 4)
    - Battle Monument (Box 4)
    - Bridge (Box 4)
    - "Constitution" (Box 4)
    - "The Late David Bachrach" (Box 4)
    - Druid Hill Park, Baltimore (Box 4)
    - Fall in Druid Hill Park, Baltimore (Box 4)
    - Landscape Around Baltimore (Box 4)
    - "Merrimac" (Box 4)
    - Paddlewheel (Box 4)
    - Portraits (Box 4)
    - Ruins of Great Fire- Baltimore, 7/28/1873 (Box 4)
    - Soldiers on Parade (Box 4)
    - Stream (Box 4)
    - Triplett, William H. (Box 4)
    - "Washington RR Station" (Box 4)
  - Photograph by Bradford Bachrach
    - Camden Street Station, Baltimore (Box 4)
  - Photographs by Fabian Bachrach
    - Portraits of men (Box 4)
    - Portraits of men (Box 4)
    - Portraits of women (Box 4)
  - Photographs of famous people
    The initials of the photographer are given in parentheses: LFB = Louis Fabian Bachrach, BB = Bradford Bachrach, and FB = Fabian Bachrach. The photographs are physically arranged in no particular order; they are listed below in alphabetical order for ease in locating specific individuals.
    - B--- Head [child] (LFB) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Dr. Walter Ames, Compton Pres., Miles Labs (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Dr. James Armstrong, Pres., Middlebury College (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Chester A. Arthur, 21st President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Lady Nancy Astor (BB), 1922 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - J. Paul Austin, President Coca-Cola Co. (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - David Bachrach, 1866 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Bachrach family [Bradford, Louis Fabian, Fabian] (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Katherine Lee Baker (Anne Thibeau) (BB), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Alexander G. Bell (DB), 1902 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - [Alexander Graham] Bell family (Oversize 1)
    - Alexander Graham Bell Family (Mrs. Elsie Bell Grosvenor, AGB, brother Melville Bell & baby Melville Bell Grosvenor) (DB), 1902 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Winton M. Blount, U.S. Postmaster General (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Fred J. Borch Pres. and Chief Exec. Officer, G.E. (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Kingman Brewster, Pres., Yale Univ. (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Warren E. Burger, Chief Justice, U.S. Supreme Court (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Billie Burke (Mrs. F. Ziegfield) (BB), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Billie Burke (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - [Billie] Burke (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Richard E. Byrd, Antarctic Explorer (FB), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Dowager Grand Duchess Charlotte of Luxembourg (BB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Dr. Rufus Clement, Pres., Atlanta Univ. (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Grover Cleveland, 22nd & 24th Pres. U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Van Cliburn (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - I.J. Collins, former Pres., Anchor Hocking Glass Co. (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - John T. Connor Chairman of the Board, Allied Chemical Corp. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Calvin Coolidge (LFB), 1925 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - [Calvin] Coolidge (LFB) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Richard Cardinal Cushing, Archbishop of Boston (FB), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Eamon DeValera, Pres., Ireland (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Thomas E. Dewey (B), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Albert B. Dick, III, Chairman of the Board, A.B. Dick Co. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - John S. Dickey, former Pres., Dartmouth College (FB), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Harris L. Dofford, Jr., Pres., Bryn Mawr College (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Harrison F. Dunning Pres., Scott Paper Co. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Thomas A. Edison (FB) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Dr. Louis K. Eilers, Pres. [Eastman] Kodak Co. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Albert Einstein, scientist (FB), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Gen. Dwight D. Eisenhower, U.S. Army (FB), 1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dr. John F. Enders, Univ. prof., Harvard and Nobel prize winner Med. (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Henry Ford (FB), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - J. Frank Forster, President, Sperry-Rand Corp. (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Felix Frankfurter, Assoc. Justice, U.S. Supreme Court (FB), 1939 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Queen Frederika (BB), Queen consort of the Hellenes, wife of King Paul of Greece (Oversize 1)
    - Queen Frederica (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Frederica, Dowager Queen of Greece (BB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Robert Frost (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - J. William Fulbright, Sen., Arkansas (FB), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - James A. Garfield, 20th President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Indira Ghandi (BB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - James Cardinal Gibbons (Baltimore) & Desire Joseph Cardinal Mercier (Primate of Belgium) (B), 1913 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Charles Dana Gibson, artist (LFB), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Godfrey (FB), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Robert F. Goheen, Pres., Princeton Univ. (FB), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Arthur Goldberg, former U.S. ambassador U.N. (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sen. Barry J. Goldwater, Sen., Arizona (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Julian Goodman Pres. National Broadcasting Co., Inc. (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - R. Burt Gookin, Pres., H.J. Heinz Co. (FB), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Lincoln Gordon, Pres., John Hopkins Univ. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Dr. Billy Graham (FB), 1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Ulysses S. Grant, 18th Pres. U.S. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Dr. Mason Gross, Pres., Rutgers Univ. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Michael L. Haider, Former President, Standard Oil Co., N.J. (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dr. Arthur A. Hanson, Pres., Georgia Institute of Technology (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Warren G. Harding, 29th President (B) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Dr. Gaylord P. Harnwell, former President, Univ. of Penn. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Benjamin Harrison, 23rd President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Roland Hayes, tenor (FB), 1943 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Rutherford B. Hayes, 19th President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Dr. David Dodds Henry, Pres., Univ. of Ill. (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Oliver Wendell Holmes, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Thomas P. Hoving (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Herbert Hoover (LFB), ca. 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey, former vice-pres. U.S. (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hussein I, King of Jordan (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Robert S. Ingersoll, Chairman and Chief Exec. Officer, Boorg-Warner (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Grand Duke Jean & mother (BB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Herbert W. Jarvis, Pres. United Shoe, Machinery Corp. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Andrew Johnson, 17th President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Dr. Sara M. Jordan (BB), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - David M. Kennedy, Sec. Treasury (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Edward M. Kennedy (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - E.K. [Edward Kennedy] & wife, JFK [John F. Kennedy] & sister (BB), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. Edward Kennedy & 2 children (BB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - John F. Kennedy (FB), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - JFK [John F. Kennedy] (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - JFK [John F. Kennedy] - JB - wedding (BB), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - John & Ted [Edward] Kennedy, K. Bennett wedding (BB), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Joseph P. Kennedy & sons (BB), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Robert F. Kennedy (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy Family, Joe, etc. (B), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy Family, Bronxville (BB), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Mohammed Ayub Khan, Pres., Pakistan (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - John F. Kiernan, sportswriter ex. (FB), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Augustus B. Kinzel, Pres. Salk Institute (FB), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Erich Leinsdorf, former Music Director, Boston Symphony Orchestra (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Col. Charles A. Lindbergh (FB), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Henry Cabot Lodge (FB), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Henry Cabot Lodge, "newly appointed ambassador to South Vietnam" (Oversize 1)
    - Henry Cabot Lodge (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Donald B. Macmillan, Arctic Explorer (FB), 1928 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Donald J. MacNaughton, President Prudential Insurance Co. of America (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Birthy Mason, Jr., Union Carbide Corp. (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - William F. May, Pres., American Can Co. (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - John McCormack, Mass. Speaker of the House (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Donald H. McGannon, Pres., Westinghouse Broadcasting Co. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - William McKinley, 25th President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Andrew W. Mellon (FB), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Thomas C. Mendenhall, Pres., Smith College (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hamilton B. Mitchell, President Dun & Bradstreet, Inc. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Raymon H. Molford, Chief Exec. Off. and Chairman, Owens-Illinois, Inc. (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Gerry Moore, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Herbert C. Moore, 31st President (FB) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Graham J. Morgan, Pres., U.S. Gypsum Co. (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Charles Munch, Conductor, Boston Symphony Orchestra (FB), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - John D. Naiper, Pres., Alcoa (FB), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Jawaharlal Nehru, Prime Minister, India (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Jawaharlal Nehru, Prime Minister (Oversize 1)
    - [Jawaharlal] Nehru leaning on hands (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Rev. Theodore M. Nesburgh, Pres., Univ. of Notre Dame (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Admiral Chester W. Nimitz (FB), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Richard M. Nixon, President U.S. (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Patricia Nixon (BB) [Mrs. Richard M. Nixon], 1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Nixon family (as candidate) (BB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Julius K. Nyerere, Pres. of Tanganyika (Tanzania) (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Sylvanus Olympio, Pres., Togo (FB), d. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Gen. Chung Hee Park, Pres., Rep. of Korea (FB), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Charles H. Percy, Senator, Illinois (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gen John J. Pershing, Comm. Amer. Expeditionary Force WWII (FB), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - John J. Powers, Jr., Pres., Charles Pfizer & Co. (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Nathan M. Pusey, Pres., Harvard University (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Edwin O. Reischauer, former U.S. Ambassador to Japan Prof., Harvard (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Abraham Ribicoff, Sen., Conn. (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - John D. Rockefeller III (FB) n.d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gov. Nelson Rockefeller (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - George Romney, Sec. Housing & Urban Development (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt (LFB), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt (different pose), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt (BB), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt, different pose (BB), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt, President U.S. (FB) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt & family (B), ca. 1918 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mr. & Mrs. F.D. [Franklin Delano] Roosevelt (B), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Theodore Roosevelt, 26th President U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 1st Roosevelt cabinet, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Harold M. Ross, former editor, New Yorker, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Elton H. Rule, Vice Pres. of ABC, pres. of Television Network Department (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Eisaku Sato, Premier, Japan (FB), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - John E. Sawyer, Pres., Williams College (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Arthur Schlesinger (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Leo H. Schoenhofen, Chairman & Chief Exec. Officer of Container Corp. of America (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Walter Scott, Chairman & Chief Exec. Officer of NBC (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Shah [Mohammad Reza Pahlavi] & Empresses of Iran (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bishop Fulton J. Sheen, (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Robert Sargent Shriver, Jr. U.S. Ambassador to France (FB), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Rear Admiral William S. Sims (FB), 1921 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Alfred E. Smith, Dem. Nom. for Pres. and Gov. of N.Y. (FB), 1928 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Geoff. Smith, President, Amstead Industries (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Maurice H. Stans, Sec. Commerce (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Vilhjalmur Stefansson, Arctic Explorer (FB), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Adlai E. Stevenson (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Vernon Stouffer, President, Stouffer Food Corp. (FB), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Rev. Raymond J. Swords, Pres., Holy Cross College (FB), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Senator Robert A. Taft, Rep. Ohio (FB), 1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - William H. Taft, 27th President (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - U Thant, Sec. Gen. UN (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Paul Tillich (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Marshall [Josip Broz] Tito, Pres., Yugoslavia (FB), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Wm P. [William Pearson] Tolley (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sekov Toure, Pres., Rep. Guinea (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Harry S. Truman, Pres. U.S. (FB) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - William V.S. Tubman, Pres., Liberia (FB), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Mark Twain with Joe Jefferson (DB), ca. 1880 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mark Van Doren (FB), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)